calculatedriskblog.com 2018-10-30

# CR4RE

* * *

## 1\. POLICY

CR4RE refers to all websites operated by CR4RE, LLC including cr4re.com, and [calculatedriskblog.com](http://www.calculatedriskblog.com/) (forwarded from [calculatedrisk.blogspot.com](http://calculatedrisk.blogspot.com/)). CR4RE, LLC (“us,” “we,” or “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of calculatedriskblog.com and CR4RE.com (“the Site”). We created this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.

You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is also a part of our Site Terms of Use, and by accessing or using our site, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions. If at any time you find these terms and conditions unacceptable, you must immediately leave the Site and cease all use of the Site.

* * *

## 2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

### 2.1. TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

#### (a) TRAFFIC DATA COLLECTED

CR4RE websites do NOT use cookies, or collect any personal information other than email addresses for a daily summary of posts. Our advertisers, or other third parties (such as commenting or site meter software) MAY use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. Most of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. CR4RE, LLC does not control the use of this technology or the resulting information and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

We allow third parties called ad networks or ad servers to serve ads to you on www.calculatedriskblog.com. This information makes it possible for the ad technology, ad servers and ad networks to deliver targeted advertisements to you on www.calculatedriskblog.com. CR4RE, LLC does not have access to the cookies that may be placed on your computer by third-party ad technology, ad servers or ad networks. CR4RE, LLC maintains relationships with a number of third-party networks, including Investing Channel and Google Adsense. Those parties that use cookies may offer you a way to opt out of ad targeting.

Here is a [link to opt out of advertising](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/)

#### (b) PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED

The only personal information collected on the site is email addresses.

### 2.2. USES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

#### (a) COMPANY USE OF INFORMATION

We may use email address Contact Data to send you information about our company or our products or services, or promotional material from some of our partners, or to contact you when necessary.

We may also use Contact Data for lead generation purpose by sending you information about products or services, or promotional material of other third party companies.

#### (b) SHARING OR TRANSFERRING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

By voluntarily signing up for emails, you are giving us your express consent to share your Personal Information with third parties in the ways described in this Privacy Policy.

* * *

## 3\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

CR4RE websites do NOT use cookies, or collect any personal information other than email addresses. 

### 3.1. USER ABILITY TO UNSUBCRIBE

We maintain a procedure to unsubscribe at any time from the email list.

Here is a [link to opt out of advertising](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/)

### 3.2. PUBLIC INFORMATION

The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We may also make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.

* * *

## 4\. PRIVACY POLICIES AND DATA COLLECTION AT THIRD PARTY SITES

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other third-party companies which place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of their cookies or other tracking technologies, which may include delivering targeted advertisements and marketing messages based upon the third party websites that you visit, or other purposes. We cannot control this collection of information and are not responsible for the privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices of these third party advertisers. You should contact these third party advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect from you. InvestingChannel is our third party ad server. If you would like to know more about their procedures, please see <http://investingchannel.com/policy>

Also, if you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>

* * *

## 5\. CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13

In compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), this Site is not directed at children under the age of 13 and we do not intend to collect any personal identifiable information, such as name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number, or social security number, from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide us with your personal identifiable information.

* * *

## 6\. PRIVACY NOTICE FOR EEA INDIVIDUALS

This section covers disclosures on the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) for users residing within EEA only. GDPR replaces the existing Directive 95/46/ec, and aims at harmonizing data protection laws in the EU that are fit for purpose in the digital age. The primary objective of the GDPR is to give citizens back control of their personal data. Please follow the link below to access [InvestingChannel’s General Data Protection Notice](http://stg.media.investingchannel.com/gdpr-notice/).

European Union (EU) laws require notice to EU visitors about cookies used on this blog. Although this blog does not use cookies, Google (blog host), Blogger, and the Ad Network does use cookies. Here are links discussing Google's use of certain Blogger and Google cookies for this blog, including Google Analytics and AdSense cookies. Learn about [Google’s privacy practices](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and how [Google uses data on partner sites](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

* * *

## 7\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.

* * *

Copyright © 2007 - 2018, CR4RE LLC, All right reserved
